Finding Aid for the Han Yu-Shan Collection LSC.1372
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Palace Examination papers by Year
  - Exam Year: Name: Ou Dayuan, 1903; R3-20; Province: Guangdong Age: 25 Rank: 3 no.146. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tang Ruitong, 1903; R3-21; Province: Guizhou Age: 34 Rank: 2 no.7. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Zengren, 1903; R3-22; Province: Zhejiang Age: 31 Rank: 3 no.100. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Hu Shangyi, 1903; R3-23; Province: Yunnan Age: 26 Rank: 3 no.80. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Kong Zhaojin, 1903; R3-24; Province: Jiangsu Age: 38 Rank: 2 no.122. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Yinchun, 1903; R3-25; Province: Zhejiang Age: 33 Rank: 2 no.41. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Zuyin, 1903; R3-26; Province: Zhili Age: 39 Rank: 2 no.133. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Geng, 1903; R3-27; Province: Shanxi Age: 32 Rank: 3 no.145. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xia Qirui, 1903; R3-28; Province: Zhejiang Age: 33 Rank: 2 no.21. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Ruiji, 1903; R3-29; Province: Shanxi Age: 30 Rank: 3 no.131. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhongxing, 1903; R3-30; Province: White Banner Age: 35 Rank: 3 no.154. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhu Deyuan, 1903; R3-31; Province: Jiangxi Age: 34 Rank: 2 no.82. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Lei Heng, 1904; R3-32; Province: Jiangxi Age: 37 Rank: 3 no.46. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Shouji, 1904; R3-33; Province: Jiangxi Age: 34 Rank: 3 no.125. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Jinkui, 1904; R3-34; Province: Zhejiang Age: 33 Rank: 2 no.106. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Luqian, 1904; R3-35; Province: Zhili Age: 33 Rank: 3 no.49. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Shiji, 1904; R3-36; Province: Jiangxi Age: 28 Rank: 2 no.87. (Box 22)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Zushen, 1904; R3-37; Province: Zhejiang Age: 27 Rank: 2 no.105. (Box 22)
- Anonymous palace examination papers., Item no. 1-10 (Box 23)
  On microfilm reel 3, items 39-48.
- Hanlin(?) Examination papers
  Year [of examination] supplied by the collector, Yu-shan Han.
  Old no.11 (microfilm R3-59) moved to the military exam group.
  - Year: Name: Yang Yong, 1694?; R3-56; Province: Shaanxi. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Yu Changce, 1706; R3-49; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Zhu Qixin, 1706; R3-50; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Shen Shu, 1723; R3-51; Province: Jiangnan. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Zhao Dajing, 1724; R3-52; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Elun, 1733; R3-53; Province: Blue Banner. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Zhu Ban'gong, 1733; R3-54; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Xu Jingxi, 1739; R3-55; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: Zhang Ying, R3-57; Province: ????. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: ????, R3-58; Province: ????. (Box 23)
  - Year: Name: ????, R3-60; Province: ????. (Box 23)
- Poem & Prose-Poem Examination papers by Year
  Year [of examinations] supplied by the collector, Yu-shan Han.
  - Year: Name: He Ruoyao, 1841; R3-70; Province: Guangdong Rank: ???? Grade: ????. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Xu Yufeng, 1841; R3-86; Province: Jiangsu Rank: 1 Grade: 17. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Chongshi, 1850; R3-64; Province: Yellow Banner Rank: 1 Grade: 11. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Fan Mingju, 1852; R3-66; Province: Hubei Rank: 1 Grade: 11. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Ren Zhaojian, 1852; R3-81; Province: Shandong Rank: 2 Grade: 3. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Yuan Chengye, 1852; R3-88; Province: Shanxi Rank: 1 Grade: 16. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Hui lin, 1860; R3-73; Province: Mengolia Rank: 2 Grade: 15. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Cao Bingze, 1865; R3-61; Province: Guangdong Rank: 2 Grade: 21. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Feng Guangxun, 1865; R3-67; Province: Jiangsu Rank: 2 Grade: 25. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Luo Jiashao, 1865; R3-79; Province: Guangdong Rank: 1 Grade: 13. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Pan Yanjun, 1865; R3-80; Province: Guangdong Rank: 2 Grade: 16. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Shi Zhibo, 1865; R3-82; Province: Fengtian Rank: 1 Grade: 22. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Tian Hanchi, 1865; R3-83; Province: Zhili Rank: 1 Grade: 18. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Zhou Kaiming, 1865; R3-91; Province: Hunan Rank: 1 Grade: 21. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Zhu Yizeng, 1865; R3-92; Province: Jiangsu Rank: 1 Grade: 23. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Gao Wanpeng, 1868; R3-68; Province: Shaanxi Rank: 2 Grade: 20. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: He Ruzhang, 1868; R3-69; Province: Guangdong Rank: 2 Grade: 27. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Hu Qiaonian, 1868; R3-71; Province: Hubei Rank: 2 Grade: 14. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Li Peiyuan, 1868; R3-74; Province: Henan Rank: 2 Grade: 5. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Li Zhaoxi, 1868; R3-76; Province: Shandong Rank: 1 Grade: 14. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Li Zhennan, 1868; R3-77; Province: Guizhou Rank: 2 Grade: 4. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Liu Zhiping, 1868; R3-78; Province: Shuntian Rank: 2 Grade: 17. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Xu Xianglin, 1868; R3-85; Province: Henan Rank: 2 Grade: 13. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Yao Xiezhan, 1868; R3-87; Province: Rehe Rank: 1 Grade: 20. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Li Minshen, 1871; R3-75; Province: Sichuan Rank: 1 Grade: 24. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Wang Zuguang, 1871; R3-84; Province: Shuntian Rank: 1 Grade: 11. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Yuan Shan, 1871; R3-89; Province: Jiangsu Rank: 1 Grade: 28. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Cao Xun, 1871; R3-62; Province: Guangxi Rank: 1 Grade: ????. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Chen Huaqiu, 1874; R3-63; Province: Guangdong Rank: 1 Grade: 60. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Zhou Jinqi, 1874; R3-65; Province: Zhejiang Rank: ???? Grade: ????. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Hu Sheng, 1874; R3-72; Province: Shuntian Rank: ???? Grade: ????. (Box 24)
  - Year: Name: Zhan Sixian, 1874; R3-90; Province: ? Rank: 1 Grade: 19. (Box 24)
- Manchu Language Examination papers by Year
  - Exam Year: Name: ????, 1655; R3-93; Province: ???? Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cao Shenji, 1655; R3-94; Province: ???? Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Da'erbu, 1655; R3-95; Province: Manchu Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Dong Se, 1655; R3-96; Province: ???? Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Qin Songling, 1655; R3-97; Province: Jiangsu Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Dai Wanglun, 1655; R3-98; Province: Zhili Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tian Fengji, 1655; R3-99; Province: Shanxi Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tian Zhongyu, 1655; R3-100; Province: ???? Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiong Chiyu, 1655; R3-101; Province: ???? Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Tian Xigou, 1661; R3-102; Province: Shanxi Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wei Jiji, 1664; R3-103; Province: Shanxi Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xiong Yixiao, 1664; R3-104; Province: Jiangxi Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Menglei, 1670; R3-105; Province: Fujian Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Hu Hui'en, 1676; R3-106; Province: Zhejiang Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Huang Huahe, 1676; R3-107; Province: ???? Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhang Rongduan, 1676; R3-108; Province: Henan Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: An Yun, 1685; R3-109; Province: Shandong Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Chen Yuanlong, 1685; R3-110; Province: Zhejiang Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wei Nan, 1685; R3-111; Province: Zhili Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Yuan, 1685; R3-112; Province: Henan Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Guan Hao, 1694; R3-113; Province: Yunnan Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Gao, 1697; [Not filmed]; Province: Jiangsu Question: Translation (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Zongfeng, 1697; R4-1; Province: Hubei Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wu Longyuan, 1700; R4-2; Province: Zhejiang Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Zhao Ziguan, 1700; R4-3; Province: Jiangxi Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Jiang Zhao, 1703; R4-4; Province: Jiangxi Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wan Jing, 1703; R4-5; Province: Zhejiang Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wan Minqin, 1703; R4-6; Province: Guizhou Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wan Minqin, 1703; R4-7; Province: Guizhou Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yang Xu, 1703; R4-8; Province: Hunan Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Cai Xuezu, 1706; R4-9; Province: Jiangsu Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Miao Rizao, 1715; R4-10; Province: Jiangsu Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Wang Mengyao, 1718; R4-11; Province: Guizhou Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Xia Kaiheng, 1718; R4-12; Province: Zhejiang Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yan Ruilong, 1718; R4-13; Province: Sichuan Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Yang Erde, 1718; R4-14; Province: Jiangnan Question: Translation. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Li Zongwan, 1721; R4-15; Province: Zhili Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Shao Tai, 1721; R4-16; Province: Jiangsu Question: Essay. (Box 25)
  - Exam Year: Name: Du Mi, 1733; R4-17; Province: Guizhou Question: Essay. (Box 25)
- Academy Examination papers
  Items 1-72 have signature of Xie Dengying (???) on cover.
  Items 73-97 have signature of Yang Yuxiu on cover.
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-18; no.265 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-19; no.472 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-20; no.174 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-21; no.23 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-22; no.287 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-23; no.32 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-24; no.105 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-25; no.15 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-26; no.6 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-27; no.53 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-28; no.42 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-29; no.28 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-30; no.84 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-31; no.96 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-32; no.219 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-33; no.179 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-34; no.423 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-35; no.122 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-36; no.99 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-37; no.64 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-38; no.42 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-39; no.75 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-40; no.133 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-41; no.172 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-42; no.189 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-43; no.195 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-44; no.8 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-45; no.49 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-46; no.137 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-47; no.64 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-48; no.308 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-49; no.51 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-50; no.100 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-51; no.53 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-52; no.334 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-53; no.155 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-54; no.162 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-55; no.64 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-56; no.40 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-57; no.77 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-58; no.88 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-59; no.83 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-60; no.40 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-61; no.43 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-62; no.4 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-63; no.372 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-64; no.226 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-65; no.???? Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-66; no.61 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-67; no.103 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-68; no.57 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-69; no.255 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-70; no.251 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-71; no.458 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-72; no.88 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-73; no.67 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-74; no.242 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-75; no.30 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-76; no.89 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-77; no.101 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-78; no.195 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-79; no.60 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-80; no.108 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-81; no.88 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-82; no.139 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-83; no.47 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-84; no.21 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-85; no.290 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-86; no.82 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-87; no.265 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-88; no.199 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-89; no.199 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-90; no.346 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-91; no.79 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-92; no.242 Subject: Da xue. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-93; no.8 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-94; no.42 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-95; no.120 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-96; no.79 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-97; no.279 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-98; no.553 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-99; no.156 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-100; no.120 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-101; no.162 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-102; no.83 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-103; no.86 Subject: Lun yu. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-104; no.355 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-105; no.316 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-106; no.277 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-107; no.242 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-108; no.60 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-109; no.105 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zhong shan, R4-110; no.225 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-111; no.78 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-112; no.103 Subject: Mengzi. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-113; no.21 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
  - Academy Name: Zun jing, R4-114; no.281 Subject: Zhong yong. (Box 26)
- Examination papers With Essays
  - Name: Bi Jinyuan, R4-115; Province: Zhejiang Age: 33. (Box 26)
  - Name: Cao Yingnian, R4-116; Province: Shandong Age: 33. (Box 26)
  - Name: Chen Qinian, R4-117; Province: Guangdong Age: 31. (Box 26)
  - Name: Chen Yanhai, R4-118; Province: Shaanxi Age: 33. (Box 26)
  - Name: Cheng Chunchu, R4-119; Province: Henan Age: 39. (Box 26)
  - Name: Gao Yongchao, R4-120; Province: Shandong Age: 29. (Box 26)
  - Name: Huang Guifang, R4-121; Province: Jiangxi Age: 36. (Box 26)
  - Name: Jiang Zhiqian, R4-122; Province: Zhili Age: 36. (Box 26)
  - Name: Kong Xianpu, R4-123; Province: Shandong Age: 48. (Box 26)
  - Name: Li Beishan, R4-124; Province: Shanxi Age: 46. (Box 26)
  - Name: Li Hongru, R4-125; Province: Zhili Age: 35. (Box 26)
  - Name: Li Jiegu, R4-126; Province: He'nan Age: 36. (Box 26)
  - Name: Li Youbo, R4-127; Province: ???? Age: ????. (Box 26)
  - Name: Liang Shicheng, R4-128; Province: Sichuan Age: 31. (Box 26)
  - Name: Rao Jiangling, R4-129; Province: Hunan Age: 29. (Box 26)
  - Name: Ren Tinghu, R4-130; Province: Henan Age: 41. (Box 26)
  - Name: Shen Maohe, R4-131; Province: Zhejiang Age: 33. (Box 26)
  - Name: Sun Rujian, R4-132; Province: Anhui Age: 32. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wang Xianzhang, R4-133; Province: Shaanxi Age: 27. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wu Mingqin, R4-134; Province: Zhili Age: 31. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wu Yongni, R4-135; Province: Shaanxi Age: 26. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wu Zongshi, R4-136; Province: Hu'nan Age: 36. (Box 26)
  - Name: Xu Baoheng, R4-137; Province: Zhili Age: 38. (Box 26)
  - Name: Xue Hongyu, R4-138; Province: Sichuan Age: 42. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yang Jun, R4-139; Province: Sichuan Age: 26. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yin Jiashu, R4-140; Province: Shandong Age: 26. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yu Kunpei, R4-141; Province: Guizhou Age: 29. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yuan Bohua, R4-142; Province: Sichuan Age: 34. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhang Jingheng, R5-1; Province: Zhili Age: 34. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhang Qin, R5-2; Province: Hubei Age: 43. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhang Zhiren, R5-3; Province: Zhejiang Age: 28. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhou Zhongyue, R5-4; Province: Jiangxi Age: 25. (Box 26)
- Examination papers With Essays
  - Name: Bai Guorong, R5-5; Province: Yellow Banner. (Box 26)
  - Name: Chen Ji, R5-6; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Chen Xiangfu, R5-7; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Chu Fenglin, R5-8; Province: Jiangsu. (Box 26)
  - Name: Cui Baoding, R5-9; Province: Jiangsu. (Box 26)
  - Name: Du Daheng, R5-10; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Gu Chiru, R5-11; Province: Jiangsu. (Box 26)
  - Name: Gu Junji, R5-12; Province: Jiangsu. (Box 26)
  - Name: Gao Cuizhen, R5-13; Province: Shanxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Guo Baoqing, R5-14; Province: Shanxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Guo Yucai, R5-15; Province: Shandong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Huang Hanhua, R5-16; Province: Guangdong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Huang Hanhua, R5-16; Province: Guangdong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Lan Guangce, R5-17; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Li Shuhan, R5-18; Province: Anhui. (Box 26)
  - Name: Lie Weiyuan, R5-19; Province: Shandong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Long Xueyi, R5-20; Province: Jiangxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Lu Qingjia, R5-21; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Luo Heying, R5-22; Province: Jiangxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Mei Rujie, R5-23; Province: Jiangxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Ou Puluan, R5-24; Province: Guangdong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Peng Yaozong, R5-25; Province: Yunnan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Peng Zuorun, R5-26; Province: Hunan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Sha ?xin, R5-27; Province: Jiangsu. (Box 26)
  - Name: Shi Tingzhu, R5-28; Province: Jiangxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Tang Qi, R5-29; Province: Jiangxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wan Hegeng, R5-30; Province: ???? (Box 26)
  - Name: Wang Jian, R5-31; Province: Jiangsu. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wang Lan, R5-32; Province: Anhui. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wang Qingbo, R5-33; Province: Zhili. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wang Songshou, R5-34; Province: Guizhou. (Box 26)
  - Name: Wei Yuqing, R5-35; Province: Yunnan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Xi Hongci, R5-36; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 26)
  - Name: Xie Yiqian, R5-37; Province: Guangdong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Xu Shici, R5-38; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Xu Siqian, R5-39; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yang Benji, R5-40; Province: Yunnan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yang Zhaozeng, R5-41; Province: Zhili. (Box 26)
  - Name: Ye Shimo, R5-42; Province: Jiangxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yin Zhengquan, R5-43; Province: Zhili. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yu Changlin, R5-44; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 26)
  - Name: Yuan Dengying, R5-45; Province: Hubei. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhang Qiren, R5-46; Province: Shanxi. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhang Erji, R5-47; Province: Sichuan. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhang Tingyu, R5-48; Province: Zhili. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhao Xirong, R5-49; Province: Zhili. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhou Zhiwei, R5-50; Province: Shandong. (Box 26)
  - Name: Zhou Zongbin, R5-51; Province: Zhejiang. (Box 26)
- Miscellaneous Examination papers
  (Items 1-7)
  - Year: Name: Gong Yongqing, R5-52; Province: Guizhou Age: 33. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Shujia, R5-53; Province: Blue Banner Age: 45. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Henggu, R5-54; Province: Red Banner Age: 31. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Saicong'a, R5-55; Province: Yellow Banner Age: 35. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Wenmao, R5-56; Province: Red Banner Age: 34. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Zhongyan, R5-57; Province: Red Banner Age: 35. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Gao Ming, R5-58; Province: Henan Age: 32. (Box 27)
- Military Palace Examination papers
  (Items 8-13)
  - Year: Name: Li Fei, 1658; R5-59; Province: Zhili Age: 32. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Li Ximing, 1712; R5-60; Province: Shuntian Age: 22. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Ma Zhengyang, 1784; R5-61; Province: Guizhou Age: 22. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Shi Jiaji, 1789; R5-62; Province: Zhejiang Age: 20. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: Yu Qianyi, 1802; R5-63; Province: Shuntian Age: 27. (Box 27)
  - Year: Name: ????, R3-59; Province: ???? Age: ????. (Box 27)
- Imperial decree, memos, etc. (Box 28, Reel 6, Box 29, Box 30, Box 31, Box 32, Box 33, Box 34)
- Positive microfilm., (2 sets). (Box 35, Box 36)